Organic molecules have been found in the Five Elder
Galaxies, and we are still far from contact with t
he third category
五老星系中发现了有机分子我们离第三类接触还有
How far away Weibo officially started the filming
mission has been seen recently
多远微博正式展开拍摄任务已经见满周年最近也
Many photos that were difficult to take in the past
were passed on to astronomers in early June
传过来许多过去难以拍摄到的照片六月初天文学家
Naturally, the photo was published on its meal, ci
rcling outside the blue core
在自然其餐上发表了这张照片在蓝色核心外还绕着
A circle of orange light, this is a galaxy-scale d
onut, which is
一圈橘黄色的光芒这是一个星系规模的甜甜圈这是
A portal, this is the surrogate ring of alien civi
lizations, in fact, this is one
一个传送门这是外星文明的代生环其实这是一个
An ancient galaxy containing organic matter polycy
clic square listening to its name is
含有有机物多环方相听的古老星系 它的名字是
SPT-0418-47 Because the name is very long, let's j
ust do it
SPT-0418-47 因为名字很长 以
下我们就
It is abbreviated as SPT-0418 and there is no abbr
eviation for this result
简称为 SPT-0418 又没有简称照
这个结果
What is the special significance of this means that
we have discovered the shape of life?
有什么特殊意义 这代表我们发现外形生命了吗
This episode of the program is a topic selected by
the members of the trafficking group, and we will
produce it every month
本集节目是贩团会员选题 我们每个月都会制作有
Topics voted by members If you have a good topic,
please us
会员投票出来的题目 如果你有好题目 希望我们
Do an episode to explain or discuss and click the
join button to become us now
做一集来讲解或讨论 马上点击加入按钮成为我们
Have you ever experienced the unfriendly division
of the workplace?
的会员吧 你是否曾经经历过职场分为不友善 充
A stressful work environment, but you don't know h
ow to deal with it
满压力的工作环境 但是你不知道如何解决呢 没
Relations, the Taipei City Labor Procuratorate Col
umn launched the number of people who violate the
workplace
关系,台北市劳动检察柱推出 职场暴力林龙人数
The teacher is hidden, and the cute leader Ava in
the teacher film will lead
位教才隐匿 教才影片里可爱的打头阿娃 将带领
You have a deep understanding of the various pace
infringements that you may face in the workplace
你们深入认识 职场可能会面临的各种步伐侵害情
Environment Through in-depth animation and profess
ional expert commentary let you understand
境 透过深动的动画与专业的专家解说 让你了解
How to face and deal with conflicts in the workpla
ce in the first place
如何在第一时间面对与处理工作场所发生的 冲突
Violence Click on the link below to watch workplace
violence Several teachers are violent in the workp
lace together, who? No, a year ago, the first group
was sent back by Wang Yuanjing on Weibo. When the
photos were shaken, we made two programs to introd
uce Weibo Wang. glasses and his importance in the
history of astronomical observations. After him, t
here were also many peddlers knocking on the bowl,
hoping that we could continue. Introducing the fol
low-up development of Weibo Wang glasses, this time
in the pre-anniversary of the public This photo of
SPT-0418 is a standard beautiful photo formed by g
ravity lens. The concept of grabbitational lansing.
I believe that those who are concerned about astr
ophysics must have heard of it. Anstein's general
theory of relativity tells us that the new system
and the new group masses will distort the space-ti
me around them, making them look like space-time A
supermagnifying glass of the new system can change
their direction when light passes through and dist
ort the image of the new system in the background.
If the new system in the background is aligned with
the new system in front of you, The gravitational
stealing effect can also distort the new system in
to a beautiful ring. This ring is called the Anste
in ring. Under the blast, the gravitational lens d
istorting the image of the background galaxy sounds
like it interferes with observation, yes. But in f
act, the gravitational lens distorts the image at
the same time
暴力 立即点入下方的连结 观看职场暴力林龙人
Focuses the light emitted by the background galaxy
so that the background galaxy becomes
数位教才 一起对职场暴力 谁?
It's brighter and easier to observe, allowing astr
onomers to see farther
no吧 一年前 在微博汪远镜传回第一组
令人震
Darker objects so although distorted images can in
crease the analysis
撼的照片时 我们制作了两期节目 来介绍微博旺
But astronomers actually like to observe these thi
ngs very much
眼镜 和他在天文观测史上 霸实代的重要意义 但
Objects affected by the gravitational lensing effe
ct will even be specially arranged for observation
他之后 也有不少贩团敲碗 希望我们可以再继续
Plan to photograph these areas affected by the gra
vity trap effect this time
介绍 微博旺眼镜的后续发展 这次在周年前戏 公
The protagonist of SPP-0418 is officially targeted
by the Mo Space Telescope
开的这张 SPT-0418的照片 是一张
标标准准
gravity trap effect in the Templash observation pr
ogram
因为重力透镜 而形成的美丽照片 重力透镜
One of the observation objects
Grabbitational Lansi
ng 这个概念
SPP-0418 is a Clock Constellation Leading the Earth
相信有在关注 天文物理的贩团们 应该都有听过
An ancient galaxy 12.3 billion light-years away was
first used by the Antarctic Telescope
安斯坦的广义相对论告诉我们 新系与新系团的
It was found in the observation data and subsequen
tly used as Atacama large good rice
庞大质量会扭曲他们周围的时空 使得时空就像
and Shiyomi Miba Town Lie, and the observations ma
de confirmed that he was a Fuhan
一面新系迟度的超级放大镜一样 可以在光线通过
A large amount of love is being received and is in
about 350 solar masses per year
时改变他们的走向 从而扭曲背景新系的影像 而
Ultra-high speed claims Hengxin's new series in our
relationship with SPT-
如果背景新系与前方的前景新系刚好前后对齐的话
Between 0418 there is also a prospect new system o
fficially this
重力偷进效应还能将背景新系扭曲成美丽的环形
The mass of the new system in the foreground disto
rts the surrounding space-time like a huge one
这个环形被称为安斯坦环炸停之下 重力透镜会
The magnifying glass of the back like this
扭曲背景星系影像这件事 听起来会干扰观察 是